35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?], circa 1954, circa 1970s; 13 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Hammersley Hill Golf Club scorecards], 19
    - [Carousel number 11 [Hammersley Hill Estate; golf (circa 1970s, circa 1954); Hawaii?]: Group picture on golf course, Lowell Thomas at right, front row], 20
  - Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people, circa 1970s, undateds; 14 (Box 1585)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people [: Pine trees, mountains in background], 1
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Road running by a lake, mountains in background], 2
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Field with mountains in the distance], 3
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Field with mountains in the distance], 4
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: A valley, mountains in the distance], 5
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Field with mountains in the background], 6
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas speaking at podium], 7
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas and three other men around golf cart], 8
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Field with mountains in background], 9
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Group of men sitting on stone steps], 10
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas talking to a crowd of people sitting on benches], 11
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas sitting on a bench with a group of other men], 12
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, their dog, and another woman in a red golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Frances Ryan Thomas with another woman], 14
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Woman holding Frances Ryan Thomas, looking over balcony at mountains], 15
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, their dog, and another woman in a red golf cart], 16
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, their dog, and another woman in a red golf cart], 17
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Road, mountains, pine trees], 18
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Wooden fence, mountains and pine trees], 19
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas walking with another man], 20
  - Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people, circa 1970s, undateds; 15 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lake and mountains], 1
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Aerial view of town], 2
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Looking up at high platform], 3
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas sitting in the snow with his dog], 4
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas sitting in the snow with his dog], 5
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas sitting the snow with his dog], 6
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: People sitting inside and talking], 7
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: People walking by lake], 8
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lowell Thomas sitting at picnic table with another man, eating], 9
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Two giraffes], 10
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Group of ostriches], 11
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Herd of elephants], 12
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lions], 13
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lions], 14
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Swans in a lake], 15
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lions], 16
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Alligator], 17
  - Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people, circa 1970s, undateds; 16 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: A house], 1
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Lions], 2
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: A house], 3
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: House on a hill], 4
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Aerial view of an estate], 5
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Little brown house], 6
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Aerial view of estate], 7
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: House], 8
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Brown house], 9
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: House], 10
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: House], 11
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: People riding in a safari boat on a lake], 12
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: House], 13
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Flowers], 14
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Roses], 15
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Aerial view of a stone building with a dome top], 16
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: (dark picture) Woman standing on a balcony], 17
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: (dark picture) Woman standing on a balcony], 18
    - [Carousel number 12 [Grand Teton National Park; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lion Country Safari (undated); unidentified houses and people]: Aerial view of neighborhood], 19
  - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places], circa 1950s, circa 1970s; 17 (Box 1585)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places] [: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in chair], 1
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas sitting in chair holding Christmas stocking], 2
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting by "Santa"], 3
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Christmas stockings laid out on desk], 4
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Woman sitting on couch, holding a Christmas stocking], 5
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Woman sitting in chair, man sitting beside her], 6
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Sunset], 7
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Sunset], 8
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Sunset], 9
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: (dark picture) Man and woman standing together on balcony], 10
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Woman standing beside a staircase], 11
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Two women standing together in a flower garden], 12
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Man and woman sitting at dining table], 13
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: "Santa" talking to an audience], 14
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas in a wheelchair in front of nativity set (?)], 15
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Woman in front of chalkboard, Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in wheelchair], 16
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas, "Santa" handing Frances a stocking], 17
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Man, dressed as a warrior, riding a horse on football field], 18
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: People sitting on bleachers], 19
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Football stadium], 20
  - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places], circa 1950s, circa 1970s; 18 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Marching band on football field], 1
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas sitting in bleachers], 2
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: People sitting in bleachers], 3
    - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Man dressed as a warrior riding a horse on a football field], 4
    - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Man taking pictures on football field], 5
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Football field], 6
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View of from inside a car, path leading to a large statue], 7
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in bleachers], 8
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View of crowd at football game], 9
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Bride walking out of church with groom, Lowell Thomas at left], 10
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Bride walking out of church with groom, Lowell Thomas at left], 11
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Bride walking out of church with groom, Lowell Thomas at left], 12
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View from boat, looking at city], 13
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas with another man on golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Grand building, palm trees (Hawaii)], 15
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View from top of a hill, looking down at city (Hawaii)], 16
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas with three other men on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas with three other men, mountains in background], 18
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Two men sitting in a golf cart], 19
  - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places], circa 1950s, circa 1970s; 19 (Box 1585)
    - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places] [: Lowell Thomas on skiis with three other people], 1
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and four other people in a parking lot], 2
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and four other people in a parking lot], 3
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Four people ice skating], 4
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas and five other people ice skating], 5
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Man and woman wearing ice skates sitting on diving board over frozen lake], 6
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Little boy sitting on grass], 7
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Man and woman standing in Lowell Thomas's broadcasting office], 8
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Lowell Thomas and another man sitting at a table, wearing suits], 9
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: People sitting at tables], 10